adzil.in 2014-02-14

# Privacy Policy - Free Classifieds in India - Adzil.in

The Privacy Policy is in relation to the information collected and practices of ADZIL. The terms of this Privacy Policy will be followed by the website. We hope these policies would address any concerns which you may have about the security of your information.

USING OUR WEBSITE WOULD MEAN THAT YOU HAVE UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

**Modifications**

The Website would have the authority to make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. It is hence advised that you read the policy from time to time.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Any information provided by you either on the website or through any published questionnaire or medium (printed as a hard copy) through which you are identifiable is termed as Personally Identifiable Information. If you wish to transact with us, information like, but not limited to, your name, mailing address (including PIN code), email address, telephone number and date of birth may be required. This information may be needed to provide relevant content to the users of Adzil.

While ordering products you might need to provide us with your credit card number, expiration date and authentication codes or related information. Depending on the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary.

If the required information is not provided, you may not be allowed to use the services of Adzil.

This information may be used, _inter alia_ , to provide products to you, enhance the operation of the Website, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze Website use, improve our product offerings, and to provide you a better experience.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that is not directly identifiable to you as an individual. This would include things like the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website you visited before coming to our Website, the URL of the website you visit after leaving our Website, the type of browser you are using and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address.

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. In the event that any advertising or promotional material is being displayed on the website, we may use this as well as Personally Identifiable Information, particularly relating to the user's location, to provide content relevant to the particular user.

**Use of Information**

Without prejudice to the preceding paragraphs, Adzil may use your information in the following circumstances:

\- When it publishes any advertising material in any format on any medium  
\- When it engages any third party service provider for providing any service or carrying on any work  
\- When requested by any law enforcement agency or Government agency  
\- With any professional requiring this information in good faith for carrying on any professional activity, such as for example a Chartered Accountant  
\- To enable viewers on the website to identify the owner / seller of a product or service and make the necessary communication to facilitate the transaction between the seller and the potential buyer. 

**Updating Information**

You will have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information you provide us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information by accessing through your login and password.

We would request you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes.

**Cookies and IP Addresses**

Your IP address, which is Personally Identifiable Information, may be used to gather demographic information about you, provide you with relevant content and also administer the website. Adzil uses cookies to deliver relevant content and save time with regards to filling information on the website.

**Security of Information**

We take appropriate precautions to protect the security of Personally Identifiable Information. You can access your Personally Identifiable Information on our Website through your login and password.

We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to.

However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, so you do so at your own risk.

**Opt-Out of Further Usage of Personal Information**

If you are no longer interested in receiving e-mail announcements and other marketing information from us, or you want us to remove any Personally Identifiable Information that we have collected about you, please e-mail your request to support@adzil.in.
